{
    "id": "b91fb8bff4ad404fb5f5f18487ea9c80",
    "title": "As Well As",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is greedy …………………………… dishonest.",
            "description": "As well as is similar to both...and..",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well as",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f22258a3749345ea944023f9397b40af"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cow as well as the goat ……………………….. us milk.",
            "description": "When we connect two singular nouns with as well as, the verb is singular.",
            "answers": [
                "give",
                "gives"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ccdf868c09a4f34846f81b3b2f19fc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief as well as his helper ……………………………. caught.",
            "description": "When we connect two singular nouns with as well as, the verb is singular.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2a4179da4a4a4d358300d4f84dcdc55e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is beautiful …………………………… intelligent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but also",
                "and",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a29233b857ec45baa455688500483953"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teachers as well as the principal …………………………….. there.",
            "description": "When you connect a plural and a singular noun with as well as, the verb agrees with the first subject in number.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6fa4d46ad1f64b3682b978023a29459d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam as well as his friends ……………………………. arrived.",
            "description": "When you connect a plural and a singular noun with as well as, the verb agrees with the first subject in number.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4cce3c7e743d421f96dec6a6974b0b4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mira as well as Rina ……………………………… gone to the movies.",
            "description": "When we connect two singular nouns with as well as, the verb is singular.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2503f05b59fd41b380b00b02efebbd5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Animals as well as plants …………………………….. food and water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "needs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "91b8c9ac37a9418bb0bf9b1e2f12c63b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Elephants are found in India …………………………… in Africa.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c07235763304262b7e03fee5e42172b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Small plants as well as big trees ……………………………. perished in the drought.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6fc63dd77db74f4e85e3de34959b6d61"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sonia as well as her parents ........................................ been invited.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "854b1d7f9978483182f34293f41b0d90"
        }
    ]
}